print("Welcome to my chatbot üòÅüòÅ")
print("Answer the 10 questions")
score = 0

questions = [
    {"question": "1. What is the full form of AI?",
     "a": "Artificial Intelligence",
     "b": "Analysis Intelligence",
     "c": "Automatic Intelligence",
     "d": "Artificial Integration",
     "answer": "a"},

    {"question": "2. Who is the CEO of Tesla?",
     "a": "Bill Gates",
     "b": "Elon Musk",
     "c": "Tim Cook",
     "d": "Satya Nadella",
     "answer": "b"},

    {"question": "3. Who is the CEO of Apple?",
     "a": "Bill Gates",
     "b": "Elon Musk",
     "c": "Tim Cook",
     "d": "Satya Nadella",
     "answer": "c"},

    {"question": "4. Who is the CEO of Toyota?",
     "a": "Bill Gates",
     "b": "Elon Musk",
     "c": "Koji Sato",
     "d": "Tim Cook",
     "answer": "c"},

    {"question": "5. Who is the CEO of Microsoft?",
     "a": "Satya Nadella",
     "b": "Tim Cook",
     "c": "Bill Gates",
     "d": "Koji Sato",
     "answer": "a"},

    {"question": "6. Who is the CEO of Nvidia?",
     "a": "Tim Cook",
     "b": "Elon Musk",
     "c": "Bill Gates",
     "d": "Jensen Huang",
     "answer": "d"},

    {"question": "7. Who is the CEO of Meta?",
     "a": "Tom Cook",
     "b": "Elon Musk",
     "c": "Mark Zuckerberg",
     "d": "Koji Sato",
     "answer": "c"},

    {"question": "8. Who is the CEO of General Motors?",
     "a": "Tim Cook",
     "b": "Mary Barra",
     "c": "Koji Sato",
     "d": "Elon Musk",
     "answer": "b"},

    {"question": "9. Who is the CEO of Google?",
     "a": "Tom",
     "b": "Sundar Pichai",
     "c": "Elon Musk",
     "d": "Koji Sato",
     "answer": "b"},

    {"question": "10. Who is the CEO of Amazon?",
     "a": "Mary Bridge",
     "b": "Tim Cook",
     "c": "Andy Jassy",
     "d": "Bill Gates",
     "answer": "c"},
]

for q in questions:
    print("\n" + q["question"])
    print("a)", q["a"])
    print("b)", q["b"])
    print("c)", q["c"])
    print("d)", q["d"])

    user_ans = input("Your answer: ").lower()

    if user_ans == q["answer"]:
        print("üëç Correct answer!\n")
        score += 1
    else:
        print("‚ùå Wrong bro!\n")

print("Your score:", score, "/", len(questions))
